<root>
   <villain name="Joker" first_appearance="April 1940">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Bill Finger" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Bob Kane" sex="male"> </creator>
   	     <creator name="Jerry Robinson" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        The Joker is a fictional supervillain created by Bill Finger, Bob Kane, and Jerry Robinson that first
   	 appeared in the debut issue of the comic book Batman (April 25, 1940) published by DC Comics.
   	 Credit for the Joker's creation is disputed; Kane and Robinson claimed responsibility for the Joker's design,
   	 while acknowledging Finger's writing contribution. Although the Joker was planned to be killed off during
   	 his initial appearance, he was spared by editorial intervention, allowing the character to endure as the archenemy
   	 of the superhero Batman.
   	 In his comic book appearances, the Joker is portrayed as a criminal mastermind.
   	 Introduced as a psychopath with a warped, sadistic sense of humor,
   	 the character became a goofy prankster in the late 1950s in response to regulation
   	 by the Comics Code Authority, before returning to his darker roots during the early 1970s.
   	 As Batman's nemesis, the Joker has been part of the superhero's defining stories,
   	 including the murder of Jason Todd&#8212;the second Robin and Batman's ward&#8212;and the paralysis of
   	 one of Batman's allies, Barbara Gordon. The Joker has had various possible origin stories
   	 during his decades of appearances. The most common story involves him falling into
   	 a tank of chemical waste which bleaches his skin white, turns his hair green, and his lips bright red;
   	 the resulting disfigurement drives him insane. The antithesis of Batman in personality and appearance,
   	 the Joker is considered by critics to be his perfect adversary.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Ra's al Ghul" first_appearance="June 1971">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Dennis O'Neil" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Neal Adams" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Ra's al Ghul (Arabic: &#1585;&#1571;&#1587; &#1575;&#1604;&#1594;&#1608;&#1604;&#8206; Ra&#702;s al-&#288;&#363;l; "Ghoul's Head" or "Demon's Head") is a fictional supervillain
   	 appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics, commonly as an adversary of the superhero Batman.
   	 Created by writer Dennis O'Neil and artist Neal Adams, the character first appeared in Batman #232's
   	 "Daughter of the Demon" (June 1971). Ra's al Ghul is one of Batman's most enduring enemies and belongs to
   	 the collective of adversaries that make up Batman's rogues gallery. Ra's al Ghul's high status as a supervillain
   	 has also caused him to come into conflict with Superman and other superheroes in the DC Universe.
   	 Ra's al Ghul is the son of Sensei, the father of Talia al Ghul, Nyssa Raatko, and Dusan al Ghul, and the grandfather of
   	 Damian Wayne. His name in Arabic has been translated in the comics as "The Demon's Head".
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Two-Face" first_appearance="August 1942">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Bob Kane" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Bill Finger" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Harvey "Two-Face" Dent is a fictional supervillain appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics,
   	 commonly as an adversary of the superhero Batman. The character was created by Bob Kane and Bill Finger,
   	 and first appeared in Detective Comics #66 (Aug. 1942). Two-Face is one of Batman's most enduring enemies
   	 and belongs to the collective of adversaries that make up Batman's rogues gallery.
   	 Once an upstanding district attorney of Gotham City and an ally of Batman, Harvey Dent goes insane after
   	 a mob boss throws acid at him during a trial, hideously scarring the left side of his face. He adopts
   	 the "Two-Face" persona and becomes a criminal, choosing to bring about good or evil based upon the outcome of
   	 a coin flip. Originally, Two-Face was one of many gimmick-focused comic book villains, plotting crimes based
   	 around the number two, such as robbing Gotham Second National Bank at 2:00 on February 2 and stealing 2 million dollars.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Riddler" first_appearance="October 1948">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Bill Finger" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Dick Sprang" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        The Riddler (Edward Nigma/Nygma) is a fictional supervillain appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics,
   	 commonly as an adversary of the superhero Batman. Created by writer Bill Finger and artist Dick Sprang,
   	 the character first appeared in Detective Comics #140 (Oct. 1948). The Riddler is a narcissist who takes delight in
   	 incorporating riddles and puzzles into his criminal plots, often leaving them as clues for the authorities and Batman
   	 to solve. The character is one of Batman's most enduring enemies and belongs to the collective of adversaries
   	 that make up Batman's rogues gallery.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Catwoman" first_appearance="Spring 1940">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Bob Kane" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Bill Finger" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Catwoman (Selina Kyle) is a fictional character appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics,
   	 commonly in association with the superhero Batman. The character was created by Bob Kane and Bill Finger,
   	 and made her debut in Batman #1 (Spring 1940), in which she is known as "the Cat." Catwoman has traditionally
   	 been portrayed as a supervillain and adversary of Batman, but since the 1990s, she has been featured in
   	 an eponymous series that cast her as an antiheroine rather than a traditional villain. Catwoman is known for
   	 having a complex love-hate relationship with Batman and has been Batman's most enduring love interest.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Simon Hurt" first_appearance="June 1963">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Sheldon Moldoff" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Charles Paris" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Dr. Simon Hurt, commonly known simply as Doctor Hurt, is a fictional character from the DC Comics universe.
   	 Hurt was revived in 2008 by writer Grant Morrison after first appearing as an unnamed character in Batman #156
   	 (June 1963). He is a brilliant psychologist whose true identity and nature is an enigma; over the course of
   	 Morrison's run he has been strongly implied at times to be the Devil, the demon Barbatos, a supernaturally-empowered
   	 ancestor of Bruce Wayne, Bruce Wayne's long-lost evil twin, Bruce Wayne's father, an instrument of Darkseid,
   	 and perhaps even Darkseid himself. Hurt is dedicated to completely destroying Batman in body, mind, and soul,
   	 and replacing him with a corrupted, evil counterpart.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Bane" first_appearance="January 1993">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Chuck Dixon" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Doug Moench" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Graham Nolan" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Bane is a fictional supervillain appearing in American comic books published by DC Comics, commonly as an adversary
   	 of the superhero Batman. The character's origin was in Batman: Vengeance of Bane #1 (January 1993), and
   	 was created by Chuck Dixon, Doug Moench, and Graham Nolan.
   	 Known for his mix of brute strength and exceptional intelligence, the character is often credited as being
   	 the only villain to have "Broken the Bat", making him one of Batman's most physically and intellectually powerful foes.
   	 IGN's list of the Top 100 Comic Book Villains of All Time ranked Bane as #34.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Penguin" first_appearance="December 1941">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Bob Kane" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Bill Finger" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        The Penguin or Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot is a fictional supervillain appearing in American
   	 comic books published by DC Comics, commonly as an adversary of the superhero Batman.
   	 Artist Bob Kane and writer Bill Finger introduced the character in Detective Comics #58 (December 1941).
   	 The Penguin is one of Batman's most enduring enemies and belongs to the collective of adversaries that
   	 make up Batman's rogues gallery.
   	 The Penguin is depicted as being short and portly, and he is known for his love of birds and his specialized
   	 high-tech umbrellas. A mobster and thief, he fancies himself as being a "gentleman of crime"; his nightclub
   	 business provides a cover for criminal activity, which Batman sometimes uses as a source of criminal
   	 underworld information. According to Kane the character was inspired from the then advertising mascot of Kool
   	 cigarettes &#8211; a penguin with a top hat and cane. Finger thought the image of high-society gentlemen in
   	 tuxedos was reminiscent of emperor penguins.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Poison Ivy" first_appearance="June 1966">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Robert Kanigher" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Sheldon Moldoff" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Poison Ivy (Dr. Pamela Lillian Isley, Ph.D.) is a fictional supervillain appearing in American
   	 comic books published by DC Comics, commonly as an adversary of the superhero Batman.
   	 Created by Robert Kanigher and Sheldon Moldoff, the character made her first appearance in Batman #181
   	 (June 1966). Poison Ivy is one of Batman's most enduring enemies and belongs to the collective of
   	 adversaries that make up Batman's rogues gallery. - Poison Ivy is depicted as one of the world's most
   	 notorious eco-terrorists. She is obsessed with plants, botany, and environmentalism. She uses toxins
   	 from plants and mind controlling pheromones for her criminal activities, which are usually aimed at
   	 protecting the natural environment. Fellow villain Harley Quinn became her recurring partner-in-crime
   	 and her girlfriend. She has proven to be one of Batman's more powerful foes, as she is one of the few
   	 members of the Dark Knight's Rogues Gallery to display anything close to superpowers. The character
   	 has been portrayed as a love interest for Batman in some comics. In one comic, she was robbing a charity
   	 gala Bruce Wayne and Barry Allen were attending. Her first kiss was poison, the second its antidote.
   	 When they first meet, her toxic lips planted a seed of toxic rapture in Bruce. But when she later kissed
   	 a dying Dark Knight, she unknowingly cured her intended victim and established a budding romantic tension
   	 between them.
      </description>
   </villain>
   <villain name="Hush" first_appearance="January 2003">
      <title>
         Top 10 Batman supervillains
      </title>
      <creators>
         <creator name="Jeph Loeb" sex="male"> </creator>
         <creator name="Jim Lee" sex="male"> </creator>
      </creators>
      <description>
        Hush is a fictional supervillain who appears in American comic books published by DC Comics.
   	 He is usually depicted as an enemy of Batman. Hush first appeared in Batman #609 (January 2003),
   	 as part of the 12-issue storyline, Batman: Hush. Hush resurfaced in Batman: Gotham Knights, and
   	 later in Detective Comics and Batman: Streets of Gotham. He has recently reemerged as the architect
   	 behind several of the events of Batman Eternal.
      </description>
   </villain>
</root>
