<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE car>
<root>

   <car name="Lexus LFA" Year_of_production="2010">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "326">
      </speed>


      <description>
       The Lexus LFA of 2010 came 10th overall. It's a mad, F1-engined coupe that Clarkson adored. The maximum speed is 326.
      </description>
   </car>


    <car name="Renault Clio" Year_of_production="1993">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "220">
      </speed>


      <description>
       The Renault Clio Williams of 1993 is renowned as one of the best handling front-wheel drive cars ever, helping it to ninth place. The maximum speed is 220.
      </description>
   </car>


    <car name="Porsche 911" Year_of_production="2000">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "270">
      </speed>


      <description>
       The Porsche 911 is 50 years old. This particular model is from 2000. In eighth place in the TG assessment of the greatest cars since then is the 993-series of the Nineties, the last of the aircooled 911s. The maximum speed is 270.
      </description>
   </car>


     <car name="Ford Focus" Year_of_production="1998">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "180">
      </speed>


      <description>
       Humble it might be, but remember that the original Ford Focus set new standards for handling when it appeared in 1998. It still looks good 15 years later, too. The maximum speed is 180.
      </description>
   </car>

     <car name="Porsche Cayman" Year_of_production="2010">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "260">
      </speed>


      <description>
        At number five is the Porsche Boxster, which attracted plaudits for its sublime handling and agility at a relatively bargain price. Year 2010. The maximum speed is 260.
      </description>
   </car>




     <car name="BMW 3-Series" Year_of_production="1999">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "220">
      </speed>

      <description>
        Why is BMW's 3-series everywhere? Because it's so good, that's why. TG readers certainly appreciate the blend of driving dynamics and remarkable fuel economy provided by the 320d, which first appeared in 1999. The maximum speed is 220.
      </description>
   </car>

     <car name="Ferrari 458" Year_of_production="2008">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "320">
      </speed>


      <description>
      At number four it's the Ferrari 458 Italia of 2008 - amazing looks, screaming V8 and Italian pedigree all wrapped up in an intoxicating package. Hard to believe it's almost four years old already. The maximum speed is 320.
      </description>
   </car>

     <car name="Rolls-Royce Phantom" Year_of_production="2003">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "260">
      </speed>


      <description>
       A surprise, perhaps, but the Rolls-Royce Phantom pipped the Ferrari to a place on the podium. Top Gear magazine staffers described it as 'sublime' when it came out in 2003 - some things never change. The maximum speed is 260.
      </description>
   </car>

     <car name="Volkswagen Golf" Year_of_production="2003">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "250">
      </speed>


      <description>
       The VW Golf GTI of 2003 is simply 'the finest hot hatch of the last 20 years' according to Top Gear magazine and its readers. The maximum speed is 250.
      </description>
   </car>

     <car name="Bugatti Veyron" Year_of_production="2006">

      <title>
         Top 10 Cars For Past 20 Years
      </title>

      <speed max_speed = "407">
      </speed>


      <description>
'Following heated discussion and a staggering response online, the Bugatti Veyron(released 2006) emerged as a worthy winner,' said Charlie Turner, editor of BBC Top Gear magazine. 'In its latest iteration, the world's fastest car costs two million euros, makes 1,187bhp and 1,107lb ft from its 8.0-litre engine, will hit 407 and burn eight litres of fuel every minute while doing so. But it is more than just a sledgehammer of physics. The Veyron is the distilled essence of the Volkswagen empire: as luxurious as a Bentley, with the build quality to put an Audi A8 to shame. Whether we will see its like again is open to question. However we do know the car industry’s desire to improve itself, its technology and its products continues to gain momentum, and the gathering pace of change is set to make the next two decades an even greater adventure'. The maximum speed is 407.
      </description>
   </car>


</root>